(Howard:)- What?
- Just whoa.
(Bernadette:)Smells pretty ripe in here.
You kind of feel it in your eyes.
(Leonard:)Raj, what's going on?
(Raj:)I was humiliated by yet another woman.
(Howard:)You didn't kill her and chop her up,
that's not what we're smelling, right?
(Raj:)No, I took her for coffee...
(Raj:)...and she snuck out the bathroom window
to get away from me.
(Bernadette:)Oh, you poor baby.
(Raj:)I went and looked.
(Raj:)It was a high and tiny window.
She must've been very motivated.
(Howard:)I'm sorry, that's awful.
- But come on, you gotta shake it off.
- You can't stay in your apartment...
(Leonard:)...for the rest of your life.
- Why not?
(Raj:)With online shopping and overnight
delivery, I can get anything I want.
(Raj:)Look, I just ordered a case
of Dinty Moore beef stew...
(Raj:)...and two live lobsters on Amazon.